# LUKE BAILEY

**Location**: Midlands

Email: lukejbailey2014@gmail.com

**Portfolio:** whiskerz1337.github.io/Portfolio

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a friendly, focused, and inquisitive Cybersecurity Graduate recently back from Australia. I aim to leverage both my strong customer service experience and my technical expertise to provide swift and effective solutions to clients.

On a more personal level, I love gaming, I speak Spanish as a second language, and have been a self-taught guitarist for over 20 years.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS SUMMARY**

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows CLIs: Unix, Windows, Cisco IOS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, Bash, Dev Ops: Git, GitHub, Docker

Rust

Cybersecurity: Incident Response, Risk Other Skills: Project Management,

Assessments, Vulnerability Scanning Strong Communication, Pair

**Programming** 

#### **EDUCATION**

PEN-200 (OSCP) Offensive Security August 2023 - Present Advanced Cert (AU) Cybersecurity August 2022 - July 2023 Cert IV (AU) Cybersecurity August 2021 - June 2022 BSc (Hons) 2.2 Music Technology 2010 - 2014

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

Data Automation Specialist (Contractor) November 2023 - Present

**1800GJ (AU)** February 2020 - August 2023

Sales, Service TTM

**Direct Line Group**EVO consultant

January 2019 - December 2019

D: 11: C

Direct Line Group January 2017 - December 2018
Landlord & Tradesmen Consultant